Quilt Alliance, Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories interviews collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Interviews
  - The Kentucky QSOS
    - Joanne Weis oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2001-08-30 (Interview-id KY40207-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 7 4x6 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR354; AFC 2007/009: SR355
  - The Kings of Quilts QSOS
    Karen Musgrave, QSOS volunteer, conducted interviews with the African American male quiltmakers who belong to the quilt group The Kings of Quilts. The group meets in Woodridge, Virginia.
    - Roy Mitchell Jr. oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-12-29 (Interview-id VA22191-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)-3 images; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_VA22191_001_06.doc; afc2007009_VA22191_001_05.jpg; afc2007009_VA22191_001_07.jpg; afc2007009_VA22191_001_08.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 digital recordings; afc2007009_VA22191_001_01.wav; afc2007009_VA22191_001_03.wav
  - The Louisiana QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Louisiana.
    - Claire Waguespack Fenton oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2006-05-19 (Interview-id LA70360-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
  - The Maine QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Maine.
    - Beth Maitland oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-11-02 (Interview-id ME04021-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_ME04021_001_03.doc; afc2007009_ME04021_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_ME04021_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR805
    - Fred Maitland oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-11-02 (Interview-id ME04021-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 2 digital documents, 4 digital images; afc2007009_ME04021_002_03.doc; afc2007009_ME04021_002_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR814
    - Cindy Verrill oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-10-17 (Interview-id ME04038-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04038_001_01.doc; afc2007009_ME04038_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04038_001_03.jpg; afc2007009_ME04038_001_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR828
    - Diane Wendorf oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-10-25 (Interview-id ME04073-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04073_001_01.doc; afc2007009_ME04073_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04073_001_03.jpg; afc2007009_ME04073_001_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR834
    - Cyndi Black oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-11-01 (Interview-id ME04350-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04350_001_04.doc; afc2007009_ME04350_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_ME04350_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04350_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR766
    - Khristine LaChance oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-08-25 (Interview-id ME04496-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04496_001_04.doc; afc2007009_ME04496_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_ME04496_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04496_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR817
    - Bonnie Dwyer oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-09-17 (Interview-id ME04531-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04531_001_01.doc; afc2007009_ME04531_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04531_001_03.jpg; afc2007009_ME04531_001_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR781
    - Elizabeth Cherry Owen oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-04-29 (Interview-id ME04553-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)–4 images; 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_ME04553_001_07.doc; afc2007009_ME04553_001_03-06.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_ME04553_001_01.wav
    - Duncan Slade oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-10-20 (Interview-id ME04556-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)–3 images; 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_ME04556_001_05.doc; afc2007009_ME04556_001_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_ME04556_001_06.wav
    - Gayle Fraas oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-10-24 (Interview-id ME04556-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)–3 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_ME04556_002_03.doc; afc2007009_ME04556_002_01.jpg; afc2007009_ME04556_002_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_ME04556_002_04.wav
  - The Maryland QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Maryland.
    - Dominie Nash oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2001-08-06 (Interview-id MD-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, color postcards, 1 brochure
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR361
    - Katharine Brainard oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2001-08-06 (Interview-id MD-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, assorted promotional material
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR362
    - Shirley Elliott oral history interview conducted by Susie Krage, 2005-12-08 (Interview-id MD20744-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Quick questions, draft and final transcript, 2 8x10 color prints, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_MD20744_001_01.doc; afc2007009_MD20744_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR363
    - Patricia Autenrieth oral history interview conducted by Susie Krage, 2005-12-14 (Interview-id MD20782-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Quick questions, draft and final transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR364
    - Susan Hinzman oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2003-01-24 (Interview-id MD20816-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR365
    - Judy Shapiro oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2003-03-05 (Interview-id MD20816-004A)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR366
    - Judy Shapiro oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2003-03-05 (Interview-id MD20816-004B)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR367
    - Linda Colsh oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2005-05-25 (Interview-id MD20816-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR368
    - Sandra Woock oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2005-03-17 (Interview-id MD20817-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR369
    - Amanda Ford oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2005-11-30 (Interview-id MD20818-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MD20818_001_03.doc; afc2007009_MD20818_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MD20818_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR370
    - Susie Krage oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2005-02-22 (Interview-id MD20850-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR371; AFC 2007/009: SR372
    - Sue Pierce oral history interview conducted by Susie Krage, 2005-06-20 (Interview-id MD20850-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Quick questions, draft and final transcript, 4 4x6 color prints, 4 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_MD20850_002_01.doc; afc2007009_MD20850_002_02-05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR373
    - Sara Brown oral history interview conducted by Susie Krage, 2003-01-24 (Interview-id MD20901-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Quick questions, draft and final transcript, 2 4x6 color prints, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 2 digital images; afc2007009_MD20901_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MD20901_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR374
    - Jeanne Benson oral history interview conducted by Susie Krage, 2005-09-02 (Interview-id MD21044-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Quick questions, draft and final transcript, 2 4x6 color prints, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MD21044_001_01.doc; afc2007009_MD21044_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_MD21044_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR375; AFC 2007/009: SR376
    - Cathy Kleeman oral history interview conducted by Susie Krage, 2006-03-23 (Interview-id MD21204-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Quick questions, final transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR377
    - Susan McKelvey oral history interview conducted by Patricia Keller, 2007-03-30 (Interview-id MD21601-001)
      MD21601-002
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_MD21601_001_02.doc; afc2007009_MD21601_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MD21601_001_03.jpg; afc2007009_MD21601_001_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR568
    - Susan McKelvey oral history interview conducted by Patricia Keller, 2007-09-21 (Interview-id MD21601-002)
      MD21601-001
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_MD21601_002_02.doc; afc2007009_MD21601_002_01.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR569
  - The Massachusetts QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Massachusetts. Also included were interviews conducted by Julie Henderson, a research assistant working with Dr. Bernard Herman, Professor of Art and Art History at the University of Delaware and QSOS volunteer. Most of Julie's interviews were facilitated with the support of Mary Walter and the patrons of her store, A Quilter's Garden, in Marlborough, Massachusetts.
    - Millie Wark oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-10-14 (Interview-id MA01535-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_MA01535_001_04.doc; afc2007009_MA01535_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MA01535_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_MA01535_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR821
    - Karen Henderson oral history interview conducted by Julie Henderson, 2002-10-21 (Interview-id MA01749-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR378
    - Susan Cummings oral history interview conducted by Julie Henderson, 2001-12-29 (Interview-id MA01749-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR379
    - Audrey Sacharkiewicz oral history interview conducted by Julie Henderson, 2001-12-29 (Interview-id MA01749-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR380
    - Ginny Ruhe oral history interview conducted by Julie Henderson, 2001-12-29 (Interview-id MA01749-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR381
    - Mary Clare Ryan oral history interview conducted by Julie Henderson, 2001-12-29 (Interview-id MA01749-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Quick questions, final transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR382
    - Mary Walter oral history interview, 2002-01-12 (Interview-id MA01749-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Quick questions
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR383
    - Joan Abshire oral history interview conducted by Julie Henderson, 2002-01-12 (Interview-id MA01749-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR384
    - Mary-Ellen Latino oral history interview conducted by Julie Henderson, 2002-01-12 (Interview-id MA01749-008)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR385
    - Sylvia Einstein oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-12-08 (Interview-id MA02478-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_MA02478_001_07.doc; afc2007009_MA02478_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MA02478_001_04.jpg; afc2007009_MA02478_001_05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 digital recordings; afc2007009_MA02478_001_02.wav; afc2007009_MA02478_001_06.wav
  - The Michigan QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Michigan.
    - Lois Beardslee oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-10-07 (Interview-id MI49664-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital images)–2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49664_001_01.doc; afc2007009_MI49664_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_MI49664_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR659
  - The Michigan State University Museum QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers at the National Folk Festival in East Lansing, Michigan, in 2001 and 2002. These interviews are also archived at the Michigan State University Museum.
    - Great Lakes Quilt Center Materials
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Great Lakes Quilt Center Correspondence, 5 pages of color digital contact prints (58 images)
    - Pauline Wolff oral history interview conducted by Debbie Ballard, 2001-08-11 (Interview-id MI48824-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript
    - Fran Mort oral history interview conducted by Fran Ballard, 2001-08-12 (Interview-id MI48824-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript
    - Unis Engle Southwell oral history interview conducted by Debbie Ballard, 2002-08-10 (Interview-id MI48824-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Elsie Vredenburg oral history interview conducted by Jan Frank, 2002-08-10 (Interview-id MI48824-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript
    - Michelle Mitchell oral history interview conducted by Jan Frank, 2002-10-10 (Interview-id MI48824-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript
    - Liz Antilla oral history interview conducted by Debbie Ballard, 2002-08-10 (Interview-id MI48824-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript
    - Gayle Cain oral history interview conducted by Mary Worrall, 2002-08-11 (Interview-id MI48824-008)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript
  - The Minnesota QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Minnesota.
    - Kate Eelkema oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-10-19 (Interview-id MN55102-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MN55102_001_05.doc; afc2007009_MN55102_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MN55102_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MN55102_001_03.wav
  - The Mississippi River Valley QSOS
    The interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, QSOS volunteer, was part of a joint project with the Illinois Arts Council and the National Endowment for the Arts through a Challenge America Grant and Quilters' S.O.S. - Save Our Stories. The project was designed to increase the awareness of the influence that the Mississippi River has had on the arts and artists of the area. The tape recorders for this project were provided by a donation from the Salt Creek Quilters Guild of Western Springs, Illinois.
    - Edna Patterson Petty oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2003-06-14 (Interview-id IL62201-01)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 4x6 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR347; AFC 2007/009: SR348
  - The Missouri QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Missouri.
    - Glenda Huffman oral history interview conducted by Vicki Quint, 2009-04-11 (Interview-id MO63010-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MO63010_001_03.doc; afc2007009_MO63010_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MO63010_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR723
    - Raymond Houston oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-08-20 (Interview-id MO63104-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout–2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MO63104_001_05.doc; afc2007009_MO63104_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MO63104_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MO63104_001_03.wav
    - Janet Ghio oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-11-18 (Interview-id MO65203-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MO65203_001_05.doc; afc2007009_MO65203_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MO65203_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MO65203_001_03.wav
    - Judy Harms oral history interview conducted by Linda Barton, 2010-11-08 (Interview-id MO65338-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MO65338_003_01.wav
  - The Naples Quilt Guild QSOS
    Joanne Gasperik and Suzanne Sanger, QSOS volunteers, have been documenting members of their quilt guild and professional quiltmakers who give guild programs since 2003. The guild meets at Emmanuel Lutheran Church in Naples, Florida. Many of the members are "snowbirds."
    - Aloyse Yorko oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2003-04-07 (Interview-id FL34106-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 4x6 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR306
    - Suzanne Sanger oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2003-04-14 (Interview-id FL34106-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Ethics statement, transcript, 2 4x6 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR307
    - Shirley Roubinek oral history interview conducted by Suzanne Sanger, 2003-05-08 (Interview-id FL34106-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 approximately 4x7 color print
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR308
    - Maryanne Olson oral history interview conducted by Suzanne Sanger, 2003-05-21 (Interview-id FL34106-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 approximately 3x5 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR309
    - Diana Steinhouse oral history interview conducted by Suzanne Sanger, 2003-05-22 (Interview-id FL34106-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 approximately 5x7 color print
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR310
    - Pat Kumicich oral history interview conducted by Suzanne Sanger, 2003-06-18 (Interview-id FL34106-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 approximately 5x7 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR311
    - Sharon Smaldone oral history interview conducted by Suzanne Sanger, 2003-07-10 (Interview-id FL34106-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Linda Franz oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2003-05-22 (Interview-id FL34106-008)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 4x6 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR312
    - Elva Zoltai oral history interview conducted by Suzanne Sanger, 2004-11-22 (Interview-id FL34106-009)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR313
    - Cathy Miller oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2005-02-16 (Interview-id FL34106-010)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR314
    - Ede Yeomans oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2005-04-07 (Interview-id FL34106-011)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR315
    - Donna Johnson oral history interview conducted by Suzanne Sanger, 2005-04-25 (Interview-id FL34106-012)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR316; AFC 2007/009: SR317
    - Naoma Morgenstein oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2005-04-09 (Interview-id FL34106-013)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR318
    - Pat LaPierre-McAfee oral history interview conducted by Suzanne Sanger, 2005-06-09 (Interview-id FL34106-014)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR319
    - Jeri McKay oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2005-04-15 (Interview-id FL34106-015)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 2 digital images; afc2007009_FL34106_015_01.jpg; afc2007009_FL34106_015_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR320
    - Sharon Schamber oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2006-03-03 (Interview-id FL34106-016)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_FL34106_016_04.doc; afc2007009_FL34106_016_01.jpg; afc2007009_FL34106_016_02.jpg; afc2007009_FL34106_016_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR534
    - Barbara Ranck oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2005-04-20 (Interview-id FL34106-017)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 2 digital images; afc2007009_FL34106_017_01.jpg; afc2007009_Fl34106_017_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR321
    - Margaret Lee oral history interview conducted by Suzanne Sanger, 2005-05-25 (Interview-id FL34106-018)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR322
    - Betty Shea oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2008-04-14 (Interview-id FL34106-019)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 4x6 color print; 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_FL34106_019_01.doc; afc2007009_FL34106_019_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR634
    - Cindy Wismann oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2008-04-14 (Interview-id FL34106-020)